Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Professional Nursing Organizations, Series 1
  - Washington State Hospital Association Publications and Materials - 1960 to 1980 (Folder 13)
  - Washington State League for Nursing Minutes and Reports - 1946 to 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Washington State Medical Association Advising Committee on Nursing Education, Annual Reports and Materials - 1947 to 1949 (Folder 2)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Administrative Materials and Activities - 1942 to 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Washington State Nurses Association and Washington State League of Nursing Education "The Washington Nursing Study" Correspondence and Materials - 1950 (Folder 4)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Conference "Rendezvous in Nursing" - 1966 to 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Conferences, Conventions, and Workshops - 1947 to 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Washington State Nurses Association, Correspondence - 1941 to 1996 (Folder 7)
  - Washington State Nurses Association "Joint Committee on Community and Rural Nursing" - 1950 to 1951 (Folder 8)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Nursing Pamphlets - 1950s to 1980s (Folder 9)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Report of a Questionnaire Study on Registered Nurses in the State of Washington" - 1961 (Folder 10)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "The Washington Nurse" - 1981 to 1982 (Folder 11)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Washington State Journal of Nursing" - 1939 to 1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Washington State Journal of Nursing" - 1960 to 1963 (Folder 2)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Washington State Journal of Nursing" - 1964 to 1965 (Folder 3)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Washington State Journal of Nursing" - 1966 to 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Washington State Journal of Nursing" - 1968 to 1974 (Folder 2)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publication, "Washington State Journal of Nursing" - 1975 to 1981 (Folder 3)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publications, Junior Journal and Mini Journal - 1971 to 1977 (Folder 4)
  - Washington State Nurses Association Publications and Questionnaires - 1950 to 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Washington State Nurses Association--Statements, Policies, and Programs - 1968 to 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Washington State Planning and Community Affairs Agency Publication "Comprehensive Health Planning--An Overview" - 1968 (Folder 7)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Agenda Books - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 8)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Conference "Annual Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Conference"--Minutes, Materials, and Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1957 to 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Conference "Proceedings of Annual Western Council of Higher Education for Nursing Conferences" - 1958 to 1963 (Folder 2)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Conference Report "Conference on Research in Nursing" - 1958 (Folder 3)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Conference Report "On-going Research Projects in Nursing in the Western Region" - 1958 (Folder 4)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Correspondence, General - 1957 to 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Project "The Continuation Education Program" - 1954 to 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Pamphlets - 1960 to 1976 (Folder 2)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Report "Newly Initiated and Completed Research" in Nursing - 1965 to 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Report "Today and Tomorrow in Western Nursing" - April, 1966 (Folder 4)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Report, Annual and Progress - 1950s (Folder 5)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Reports on Organizational Restructuring - 1970s (Folder 6)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Seminar on Continuing Education--Materials - 1957 to 1972 (Folder 7)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Conference "Leadership in Nursing"--Hilda B. Roberts Notes and Materials - 1957 to 1960 (Folder 8)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Conference "Leadership in Nursing"--Reports - 1957 to 1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Conference "Leadership in Nursing"--Reports - 1959 to 1960 (Folder 2)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Conference "Western Conference on Nursing Education"--Materials - 1955 to 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Correspondence, General - 1956 to 1976 (Folder 4)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Correspondence with Hilda B. Roberts - 1955 to 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Nursing Education Monographs No. 1 and 2 - 1968 (Folder 6)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Pamphlets - 1954 to 1975 (Folder 7)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Project "Curriculum Improvement Project" Materials - 1967 to 1971 (Folder 8)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Publication "Communicating Nursing Research" Vol. 01-04 - 1968 to 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Publication "Defining Clinical Content: Graduate Nursing Program" 3 vol. - 1967 (Folder 2)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Publication "Reports on Higher Education" - 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Publications on Changes in Western Nursing Education - 1956 to 1964 (Folder 4)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Publications on Nursing Education - 1956 to 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Report "Annual Report" - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 6)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Report "Nurses for the West" - 1959 (Folder 7)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education / Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing Membership Rosters - 1972 to 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Western Schools for Advanced Education in Nursing Correspondence with Hilda B. Roberts - 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Western Washington League of Nursing Education, Conference Materials - 1952 to 1954 (Folder 3)
  - Western Washington State College Nursing Program Materials - 1977 (Folder 4)
  - Whitman County Civil Defense Committees, Materials and Correspondence - 1951 to 1963 (Folder 5)
  - Whitman County Nurses Association: Conference on Hospital Infections - March 13, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Whitman County Nurses Association Conference on Hospital Infections Pictures and Publicity - 1959 (Folder 7)
  - Whitman County Nurses Association, Correspondence - 1959 to 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Whitman County Nurses Association, Newsletters - 1964 to 1996 (Folder 9)
  - Whitman County Nurses Association Newspaper Articles - 1956 to 1968 (Folder 10)
  - Whitman County Nurses Association, Washington State Nurses Association Materials/Newsletter - 1964 to 1974 (Folder 11)
- Washington State College (WSC) School of Nursing, Series 2
  - WSC Administration Memos to Deans and Department Heads - 1945 to 1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Hospital Histories and Brochures - 1948 to 1956 (Folder 2)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Newspaper Articles on St. Luke's Hospital - 1944 to 1988 (Folder 3)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing--Nursing Procedure Binder - 1950s (Folder 4)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Organizational and Administration Materials - 1944 to 1956 (Folder 5)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of Classes and Clinical Experience - 1940s to 1955 (Folder 6)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Diet Therapy" - 1944 to 1955 (Folder 7)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Medical/Surgical Nursing" - 1950 to 1955 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Nursing Arts Practice" - 1944 to 1955 (Folder 2)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Nursing Conferences and Displays" - 1948 to 1959 (Folder 3)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Obstetrics" - 1954 to 1955 (Folder 4)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Occupation and Physical Therapy" - 1955 (Folder 5)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Pediatrics-Shriners" - 1951 to 1955 (Folder 6)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of Pediatrics and Maternity Nursing--St. Luke's Hospital - 1940s to 1955 (Folder 7)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of Polio Ward - 1955 (Folder 8)
  - WSC and ICNE School of Nursing Photographs of Scholarships and Awards - 1950s to 1998 (Folder 9)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of Student Nurses Helping and Teaching Patients - 1955 to 1970s (Folder 10)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Photographs of "Students in Labs" - 1954 to 1955 (Folder 11)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing "Student Health Program" - 1944 to 1947 (Folder 12)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Survey Visits by Various Nursing Personnel - 1944 to 1971 (Folder 13)
  - WSC--College Extension Program "Community College Service" Correspondence with Nursing Faculty - 1941 to 1957 (Folder 14)
  - WSC--College Extension Program "Community College Service" Materials on Nursing Education - 1946 to 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - WSC--College Extension Program "Continuing Education Program in Nursing" - 1957 to 1958 (Folder 2)
  - WSC--College Extension Program "Junior College Transfer Program" for Nursing Students, Materials and Correspondence - 1949 to 1964 (Folder 3)
  - WSC--College Extension Program "Junior College Workshop" Materials - 1950 (Folder 4)
  - WSC--College Extension Program Nursing Refresher Courses Materials and Publicity - 1947 to 1966 (Folder 5)
  - WSC--College Extension Program "Washington State Public Health Training Program" Materials and Correspondence - 1945 to 1962 (Folder 6)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Agreements with St. Luke's Hospital, Spokane to Establish Integrated Nursing Program - 1945 to 1955 (Folder 7)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Agreements with Various Washington Health Organizations - 1944 to 1957 (Folder 8)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Deaconess Hospital Nursing School - 1944 to 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Eastern State Hospital Medical Lake, WA - 1943 to 1951 (Folder 2)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Nursing Schools and Hospitals in Idaho - 1946 to 1957 (Folder 3)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Sacred Heart School of Nursing Spokane, WA - 1941 to 1951 (Folder 4)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with St. Elizabeth School of Nursing Yakima, WA - 1946 to 1948 (Folder 5)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with St. Luke's School of Nursing - 1945 to 1953 (Folder 6)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Saint Mary School of Nursing Walla Walla, WA - 1945 to 1950 (Folder 7)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Shriner's Hospital, Spokane - 1951 to 1956 (Folder 8)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with Various Washington State Schools of Nursing - 1949 to 1956 (Folder 9)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Faculty Correspondence with WSC Division of Properties - 1944 to 1951 (Folder 10)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Newsletter - 1947 to 1951 (Folder 11)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Reports on Nursing Department Activities to WSC Administration - 1939 to 1953 (Folder 12)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Materials for Director Bertha Davis - 1939 to 1941 (Folder 13)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Materials for Director Betty Anderson - 1945 to 1964 (Folder 14)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Materials for Director Chesta Hayden - 1945 to 1952 (Folder 15)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Materials for Director Grace Gray - 1944 to 1945 (Folder 16)
  - WSC Department of Nursing Education Materials for Director Helen M. Platt - 1942 to 1943 (Folder 17)
  - WSC Nursing Facilities Photographs - 1950s (Folder 18)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Advisor Assignments and Correspondence - 1947 to 1977 (Folder 19)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Correspondence with St. Luke's School of Nursing - 1944 to 1949 (Folder 20)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Correspondence with St. Luke's School of Nursing - 1950 to 1957 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Faculty Travel Authorizations - 1950 to 1952 (Folder 2)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Inventories of Property and Lab Equipment - 1936 to 1986 (Folder 3)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Non-Faculty Personnel Materials and Correspondence - 1947 to 1950 (Folder 4)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Policies and Procedures - 1953 to 1955 (Folder 5)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Policies and Procedures of Good Samaritan School of Nursing, Portland, OR - 1950s (Folder 6)
  - WSC School of Nursing Administration Rosters and Teaching Assignments - 1952 to 1956 (Folder 7)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions and Recruitment Faculty Correspondence - 1946 to 1952 (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions and Recruitment "High School Visitation Program" Materials and Correspondence - 1948 to 1955 (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions and Recruitment Letters - 1945 to 1965 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions Application, Forms, and Materials - 1950s (Folder 11)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions Correspondence with Faculty - 1945 to 1952 (Folder 12)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions Correspondence with Prospective Students - 1944 to 1952 (Folder 13)
  - WSC School of Nursing Admissions Enrollment and Graduation Data - 1939 to 1978 (Folder 14)
  - WSC School of Nursing Affiliation on Public Health Nursing with Various Institutions - 1946 to 1953 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - WSC School of Nursing Affiliation on Psychiatric Nursing with Eastern State Hospital Materials and Correspondence - 1941 to 1956 (Folder 2)
  - WSC School of Nursing Affiliation on Tuberculosis Nursing with Veterans Administration Hospital Walla Walla, WA; Materials and Correspondence - 1948 to 1955 (Folder 3)
  - WSC School of Nursing "Conference on Hospital Infections" - 1959 (Folder 4)
  - WSC School of Nursing Conference "The Nurse's Responsibility in Fluid and Electrolyte Balance" - 1959 (Folder 5)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Activities Newspaper Articles - 1948 to 1997 (Folder 6)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Correspondence on Nursing Photographs - 1949 to 1964 (Folder 7)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Correspondence on Policies and Curriculum with Out-of-State Universities - 1943 to 1971 (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Correspondence with Chairman of Division of Biological Sciences, W. R. Hatch - 1949 to 1952 (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Correspondence with WSC Administration - 1940 to 1960 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Memos and By-laws - 1950s (Folder 11)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty "Nursing Procedure Book" - 1950 to 1960 (Folder 12)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Orientation - 1952 to 1967 (Folder 13)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Recruitment Correspondence - 1947 to 1964 (Folder 14)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Recruitment Job Descriptions and Announcements - 1949 to 1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Reviews and Promotions - 1954 to 1957 (Folder 2)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Workshops - 1953 to 1958 (Folder 3)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Course Catalogue and Revisions - 1950s (Folder 4)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Curriculum Development Materials and Publications - 1948 to 1965 (Folder 5)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Curriculum Development Sample Class Schedules - 1947 to 196 (Folder 6)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Curriculum Development Statements, Plans, and Revisions - 1943 to 1958 (Folder 7)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Descriptions and Information - 1948 to 1958 (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Discontinuation Materials and Correspondence (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Materials for the Historical Collection - 1946 to 1982 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Newspaper Articles - 1945 to 1966 (Folder 11)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Pamphlets and Brochures - 1943 to 1960s (Folder 12)
  - WSC School of Nursing Program Philosophy and Objectives Statements - 1945 to 1958 (Folder 13)
  - WSC School of Nursing Registration Class Lists and Student Rosters - 1940s to 1950s (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - WSC School of Nursing Registration Correspondence - 1943 to 1958 (Folder 2)
  - WSC School of Nursing Report " Where Do We Get Our Supply of Nurses in This State?" By Hilda B. Roberts - 1954 (Folder 3)
  - WSC School of Nursing Report on "The Formulation of a Plan for Filing and Indexing Applicable to the State College of Washington School of Nursing Office - 1957 (Folder 4)
  - WSC School of Nursing Reports on St. Luke's School of Nursing - 1951 to 1954 (Folder 5)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Evaluation Criteria and Materials - 1950 to 1968 (Folder 6)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Hospital Rotations and Clinical Schedules - 1945 to 1959 (Folder 7)
  - WSC School of Nursing United States Cadet Nurse Corps Photographs - 1945 to 1946 (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing United States Cadet Nurse Corps Program Faculty Correspondence - 1943 to 1951 (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing United States Cadet Nurse Corps Program Materials - 1943 to 1949 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing United States Cadet Nurse Corps Quarterly Enrollment Reports - 1943 to 1949 (Folder 11)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1941-1943 Materials and Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1943-1945 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 2)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1945-1947 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 3)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1947-1949 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 4)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1949-1951 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 5)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1951-1953 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 6)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1953-1955 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 7)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1955-1957 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 8)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1957-1959 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 9)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1959-1961 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 10)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1961-1963 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 11)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1963-1965 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 12)
  - WSU Biennial Budget for Nursing Program 1965-1967 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 13)
  - WSU Nursing Program Departmental Budget Summary - 1947 to 1965 (Folder 14)
- Washington State College (WSC)Nursing Faculty Organizations, Series 2A
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Joint Committee on Nursing Education, Correspondence - 1941 to 1954 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Joint Committee on Nursing Education; Minutes, Reports, and Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1941 to 1956 (Folder 2)
  - WSC--College Hospital and Health Advisory Committee (Campus Health Committee) Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence - 1943 to 1947 (Folder 3)
  - WSC School of Nursing Committee on Student Affiliation in Public Health Nursing Minutes, Materials, and Correspondence - 1948 to 1953 (Folder 4)
  - WSC School of Nursing Curriculum Committee Minutes and Materials - 1951 to 1956 (Folder 5)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Committee Schedules, Rosters, and Correspondence - 1951 to 1957 (Folder 6)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Executive Committee Minutes - 1954 (Folder 7)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Meeting Minutes and Materials - 1948 to 1954 (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Meeting Minutes and Materials - 1955 to 1957 (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing Faculty Personnel Committee Minutes and Correspondence - 1955 to 1956 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing Hospital-School Conference Committee Minutes - 1956 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - WSC School of Nursing Joint Public Health and Hospital Directors Committee Minutes and Correspondence - 1945 to 1948 (Folder 2)
  - WSC School of Nursing Library Committee Minutes - 1945 to 1956 (Folder 3)
  - WSC School of Nursing Procedure Committee Minutes - 1952 to 1955 (Folder 4)
  - WSC School of Nursing (Clinical) Rotation Committee Minutes - 1952 to 1953 (Folder 5)
  - WSC School of Nursing Scholarship and Standards Committee Materials, Awards, and Correspondence - 1951 to 1966 (Folder 6)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Health and Welfare Committee - 1952 to 1955 (Folder 7)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Personnel Committee Minutes - 1955 to 1957 (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Records Committee Minutes - 1955 to 1956 (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Welfare and Recruitment Committee, Minutes - 1952 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing Sub-Committee on Counseling and Guidance, Minutes - 1955 to 1956 (Folder 11)
  - WSC School of Nursing Sub-Committee on (Student) Health, Minutes - 1955 to 1957 (Folder 12)
  - WSC School of Nursing Sub-Committee on social and Recreational Activities Minutes - 1955 to 1956 (Folder 13)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education (ICNE), Series 3
  - ICNE Administration Academic Calendars and Course Schedules - 1969 to 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence General Faculty Memos - 1970 to 1975 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence of Dean Grace Deloughery - 1972 to 1973 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence of Dean Laura Dustan - 1975 to 1981 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence of Dean Thelma Cleveland - 1970 to 1989 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence of Faculty Betty M. Anderson - 1966 to 1979 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence of Faculty Flora Green - 1966 to 1968 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence with Dean of Division of Sciences B. R. Ray - 1968 to 1977 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence with Dean of Division of Sciences Robert A. Nilan - 1976 to 1982 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence with Vice President of Academic Affairs Alan Smith - 1968 to 1977 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Administration Correspondence with Vice President of Finance V. C. Shelton - 1967 to 1981 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Administration Dedication and Retirement Ceremonies - 1978 to 1980s (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Administration Descriptions of Staff Positions - 1971 to 1982 (Folder 13)
  - ICNE Administration Events, Conferences, and Workshops; Newspaper Articles - 1960s (Folder 14)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty and Staff Position Announcements - 1970 to 1978 (Folder 15)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Biographical Data and Personnel Questionnaires - 1946 to 1982 (Folder 16)